

email: kovagozsofia@gmail.com

mobile: +36 70 241 5424

GitHub zsofi777 Linked in www.linkedin.com/in/kovagozsofia 🕪





#### **SUMMARY**

I worked as a Statistical Analyst and Supervisor in four international projects the last three years, so I originate the passion for coding by using several statistical programs. After participating in GFA's winter coding camp last year I instantly knew that I will be a tech woman.

#### **MOTIVATION**

I cherish progress, evolution and intellectually interesting work, and I love to explore new ideas. Also, the flexibility, independency and like-minded people are appealing.

### WORKSHOP TECHNOLOGY C / C++

#### PROJECT PHASE TECHNOLOGY

- HTML MongoDB Redux
- CSS Express.js React
- TypeScriptJavaScript
- MySQL Redux Saga

#### **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH** fluent **HUNGARIAN** native

# Zsófia Kővágó

JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

# **EDUCATION**

2010-2012

**EÖTVÖS LORÁND UNIVERSITY** 

SURVEY STATISTICS MSc degree

2003-2005

**BUDAPEST BUSINESS SCHOOL** 

TRADE MANAGER Advanced Vocational Qualification (OKJ)

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2016-2019

RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR NATIONAL STRATEGY

RESEARCH SPECIALIST

• Statistical Analyst and Supervisor in macro-regional HRDOP projects

2012-2016

MINISTRY FOR NATIONAL ECONOMY

STATISTICAL ANALYST

• Subject Expert and Statistical Analyst in a SROP project

2011

MAVEN SEVEN NETWORK RESEARCH INC.

DATA MINER

• Extract Data from Medical Databases



FRONTEND M DEVOPS □ BACKEND

FULL-STACK ★ TEST-AUTOMATION □

DATA SCIENCE □ EMBEDDED □

